tamucc.edu 2004-06-04

# Privacy Statement

Main \- Privacy Statement   
Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi maintains this web site as an information resource and service for the public. In the course of providing you this information, we are able to gather and archive several types of data about visitors to our web site. In respect to your privacy and in accordance with State law, the following outlines how we handle those types of data. 

**Personally Identifiable Information.** Personal information that you provide via e-mail or through other online means will be used only to respond to your request or to analyze trends. This may involve redirecting your inquiry or comment to another person or department who is in a better position to answer your question or meet your needs.

The University accumulates data and keeps records to enable staff and faculty to plan educational opportunities to meet the needs of individual students, to better understand students, to counsel more effectively with them and to assist them in placement in graduate education or employment after graduation. Provisions are made for students to review and challenge the accuracy of records when appropriate and upon request. The University also complies with the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act of 1974 and with the Texas Public Information Act.

Some directory information (e.g., home address, local address, local telephone number, etc.) given to the University is considered public information and will be released by the University upon request, in accordance with existing law. Someone who does not wish this public information to be released must notify the appropriate offices within the University. For more information, see the "Student Records Policy" in the University Catalog and [TAMUS Regulation 61.01.02](http://sago.tamu.edu/policy/61-01-02.htm).

For various management functions including site development, recruitment, and retention tracking, personal information may be used for analysis and statistical purposes. This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless the University is legally required to do so.

**Cookies.** The main A&M-Corpus Christi web site (www.tamucc.edu) does not use cookies to collect information, although other subsections of our web site may do so. Cookies are files maintained within your browser that allow websites to track things like passwords, pages you have visited, the date you last looked at a specific page, and to identify your session at a particular Web site. Any subsections of our web site that do use cookies will have a separate privacy statement outlining how information collected is used.

**Server Logs.** A&M-Corpus Christi uses server logs to collect information concerning your Internet connection and general information about your visit to our Web site. This information may be used to analyze trends; to create summary statistics for the purpose of determining technical design specifications; and to identify system performance or problem areas. The following information may be collected for this analysis including, but not limited to:

  * User/client hostname - The hostname (or IP address if DNS is disabled) of the user/client requesting access
  * HTTP header, "user agent" - The user-agent information includes the type of browser, its version, and the operating system it is running on
  * HTTP header, "referrer" - The referrer specifies the page from which the client accessed the current page
  * System date - The date and time of the user/client request
  * Full request - The exact request the user/client made
  * Status - The status code the server returned to the user/client
  * Content length - The content length, in bytes, of the document sent to the user/client
  * Method - The request method used
  * Universal Resource Identifier (URI) - The location of a resource on the server
  * Query string of the URI - Anything after the question mark in a URI
  * Protocol - The transport protocol and version used

**Links.** This web site contains links to other sites not owned or maintained by the University; Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi is not responsible for the content or privacy policies on those sites.

**Security.** This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

**Contact.** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your use of this Web site, you may contact the [University Web Coordinator](mailto:pioweb@falcon.tamucc.edu) or through regular mail at:

    University Web Coordinator
    Texas A&M University-Corpus Christi
    University Services Center 107
    6300 Ocean Drive
    Corpus Christi, TX 78412

_Return to top_
